ILGWU Apparel Job Training and Research Corporation Records 5780/114
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Tarrytown Garment Co. Enrollee Applications. 2-200118-TA021., 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 53)
- Temple Industries.1-200513-TE031., 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 54)
- Temple Industries. Enrollee Applications. 1-200513-TE031., 1980 (Box 15, Folder 55)
- Temple Industries. 1-200513-TE032., 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 56)
- Temple Industries. Enrollee Applications. 1-200513-TE032., 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 57)
- Terry Ann Sportswear 1-200518-MA041, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Terry Ann Sportswear Enrollee Termination 1-200518-MA041, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Tim Sportswear 1-200913-NB041, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Tim Sportswear Enrollee Applications 1-200913-NB041, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Toyed Sportswear 1-201524-NY011, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Toyed Sportswear Enrollee Applications 1-201524-NY011, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Val Sportswear 1-220112-WB031, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Val Sportswear Enrollee Applications 1-220112-WB031, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Valerie Sportswear 1-220112-WG031, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Valerie Sportswear Enrollee Applications 1-220112-WG031, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- W.E.B. Sportswear 1-230502-FR041, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- W.E.B. Sportswear Enrollee Applications 1-230502-FR041, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Woodbury Manufacturing 1-221515-WB032, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Woodbury Manufacturing Enrollee Applications 1-221515-WB032, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Ace High Fashions 1-010305-NY011, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Alba Fashions 1-011202-CL021, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Alma Dress 1-011213-SD031, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- American Bazaar 1-011305-NB051, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Amy Togs 1-011325-WB031, 1979-1981 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Andy's Sportswear 1-011404-BO041, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Angie Clothing 1-011407-NB011, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Ann Rett Dress 1-180520-NY011, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Ann Jon Dress Corporation 1-011414-NY011, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Arian Fashions 1-011809-VI021, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- B and B Manufacturing 2-020519-NY011, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Belfiore Dress Corporation 1-020512-NB011, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Berwick Mills 2-020518-NB241, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Best Knitting 2-020519-NY011, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Betcyan 1-020520-FR042, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Brade Sportswear 1-021801-PA021, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Brodsky, Louis, and Son 1-021804-SR021, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Brookmay Manufacturing 1-021815-NB011, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Cabaret, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Cambridge 1-030113-FR041, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Capitol Swimwear 1-030116-HT053, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- Chester Apparel 1-030805-CH031, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 36)
- Christopher-Jo 1-030818-FO031, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 37)
- Concord Manufacturing 1-031514-MO072, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Crescent Lingerie 1-031805-BE011, 1979-1981 (Box 16, Folder 39)
- D.J. Dress 1-041004-NY013, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 40)
- David Stevens Manufacturing 1-040122-BL023, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 41)
- Doris Ann Fashions 1-041518-UC022, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 42)
- Dresscraft 1-041805-WY021, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 43)
- Elaine Frocks 1-051201-AV031, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 44)
- Family Fashion 1-060109-FR041, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 45)
- Family Garment 1-060113-SC031, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 46)
- Forecaster of Boston 2-061518-BO041, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 47)
- Ian Murray 1-090114-BR041, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 48)
- Irene Sportswear 1-091805-WI031, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 49)
- J and R Dress 1-101804-WY033, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 50)
- Jai Screen Printing 2-100109-NY011, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 51)
- Jay Cee Manufacturing 1-100125-CB031, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 52)
- Jeff Manufacturing 1-100506-TT031, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 53)
- Joel Manufacturing 1-101505-WB031, 1979-1981 (Box 16, Folder 54)
- K Sportswear 1-111916-CB031, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 55)
- Kay Windsor 2-110125-NO041, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 56)
- Kim and Jim 1-110913-FR041, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 57)
- Kravif Manufacturing 1-111801-FR041, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 58)
- Lehigh Dress 1-120508-BE031, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 59)
- Lindy Sportswear 2-120914-BO041, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 60)
- Lisa Sportswear 1-120919-WB033, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 61)
- Loring Coat 2-121518-NB011, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 62)
- M. Dara Dress 1-130401-RF021, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 63)
- Maranda 1-130118-SG011, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 64)
- Marlene Undergarment 3-130118-NY011, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 65)
- Merit Dress 1-130518-PS021, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 66)
- Miss A Couture 1-130919-NY011, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 67)
- Muriel Pembroke 1-132118-BE031, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 68)
- Nan's Sportswear 1-14011-HO031, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 69)
- Nardi Sportswear 1-140118-BR041, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 70)
- New City Sportswear 2-140523-HA011, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 71)
- P and K Dress 1-161104-LF011, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 72)
- Paramount Coat 1-160118-CA041, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 73)
- Parsley Apparel 1-160118-RO011, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 74)
- Patty Ann Fashions 1-160120-CB031, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 75)
- Pawtucket Dress 1-160123-PW061, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 76)
- Perri Sportswear 1-160518-PK011, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 77)
- Piccento Sportswear 1-160903-BR041, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 78)
- Prattville Apparel 1-161801-CH081, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 79)
- Prattville Apparel 1-161801-MG221, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 80)
- Quality Apparel 1-172101-BU021, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 81)
- R and K Apparel 1-181101-PM031, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 82)
- Reid Steven 1-180509-CK011, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 83)
- Reliable Sportswear 1-180512-FR041, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 84)
- Rita Sportswear 1-180920-MO031, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 85)
- Riverview Sportswear 1-180922-RI021, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 86)
- Rob-Anne Sportswear 1-181502-CH031, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 87)
- Rosalee Casuals 1-181519-NY011, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 88)
- Rosetta Formals 1-151905-NY011, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 89)
- Rovin Dress 1-181522-JC021, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 90)
- Sambark Coat 1-190113-GV011, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 91)
- Sands Manufacturing 1-190114-NY011, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 92)
- Sa-Ra's Manufacturing 1-190118-NY011, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 93)
- Sayre Lingerie 1-190125-SA032, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 94)
- Sew-M-Up 1-190523-NY011, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 95)
- South Bay Coast 2-191521-FR041, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 96)
- Star Fashions 1-192001-FR041, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 97)
- Starlette Sportswear 1-192001-NY011, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 98)
- Sunflower Novelty Bag 2-192114-DP011, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 99)
- Suz-Ette Fashions (Cohoes Garment) 1-192126-AB011, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 100)
- Suz-Ette Fashions (G.C. Fashions) 2-192126-GC011, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 101)
- Suz-Ette Fashions (L and S Fashions) 2-192126-AV011, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 102)
- Trestina Dress Manufacturing 1-201805-NY011, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 103)
- Universal Coat Company 1-211409-BA011, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 104)
- Wallace-Lookout Fashions 1-230112-BO031, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 105)
- Zodiac Sportswear 1-261514-NY011, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 106)